http://www.collegesavings.com/privacy

Privacy
Download our Privacy Notice »
Protect Yourself from E-Mail Fraud
As a general rule, never send credit card information, account passwords, or extensive personal information in an email. College Savings Bank, a Division of NexBank will never ask you for any type of personal information by e-mail.
We value your privacy. That is why we do not request personal information via e-mail. If you receive an e-mail that appears to be from College Savings Bank, a Division of NexBank, and the message asks you for personal information such as your social security number, account number, or other sensitive information, DO NOT RESPOND to the e-mail. It is not from College Savings Bank, a Division of NexBank. It is a hoax designed to deceive you into sharing personal information with identity thieves.
This type of e-mail fraud targets customers of reputable companies and is being used with great frequency by scam artists. Typically, the e-mail warns you of some problem with an account or promotes a special offer and directs you to a web site that appears to belong to a legitimate company. In fact, the web site is fake and any information you provide may be used fraudulently.
Privacy Safety Tips:
Be suspicious of any e-mail that asks for personal information, requests your authentication, or indicates a problem with your college savings account.
Be aware that legitimate companies do not ask customers to verify personal information by sending e-mail or pop-up ads.
Never respond to an e-mail asking for your credit card information.
Avoid sending personal and financial information by e-mail.
Never click on a link in an e-mail if you are unsure of its origins, especially if the e-mail asks for personal financial information.
If you receive a questionable e-mail that contains our name or logo, do not reply by e-mail and do not click on any links. Call the us at 1-800-888-2723.
Effective date 7/2020
